# **Zoheb Khan**

zoheballikhan@gmail.com +91 9337152352 Rourkela, Odisha

### **Summary**

18-year-old programmer who enjoys developing software. For the past three years, I have been involved in the programming community for 3 years now with an interest in fintech and developer toolchain products. I was a software engineer intern at Helmer.

### **Experience**

# Software Engineer Intern

Helmer

09/2023 - 02/2024

- Worked on an internal developer tool, scap, which was a cross-platform screen-capture library.
- Developed little UI/UX of Helmer-Micro, MVP of Helmer.

# Software Engineer Intern

CloudQA • Hyderabad, Telengana 03/2023 - 05/2023

• Built applications with ASP.NET and everything surrounding the C#(.NET) ecosystem

#### Research Intern

International Institute of Information Technology, Bangalore

10/2022 - 02/2023

- · worked under the assistance of Prof. S.K. Chakraborty
- · learnt about interpreter and compiler systems and how to build one
- Contributed to project such as statechart-verification

## LimboHacks

Organizer

07/2021 - 11/2021

- Collaborated with 5 other organizers from around the globe
- Maintained the codebase of the microservices, managed mentors, participants

### **Projects**

- <u>pbudget</u> rust, actix web, jwt-auth Personal Budget API
- <u>bwdm</u> pcap, golang Bandwidth Monitoring CLI-TUI
- <u>rustfuscator</u> rust, regex Javascript Obfuscator
- ws-cli rust Web Scraper CLI

#### **Books and Publications**

Zoheb Khan, Notionpress, 2022, Hypebeast: Building web apps with Typescript, Node.js, React.js, PostgreSQL

#### **Skills**

HTML&CSS, React, C++, SQL, Java, Git, Python, Javascript, GraphQL, Node.js, Golang, Communication skills

# Education

# **High School**

Deepika English Medium School • Rourkela 03/2024